expeditelectronics.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy

**PRIVACY POLICY**

**Expeditelectronics.com** takes your privacy seriously, and we want you to know how we collect, use, share and protect your information.

**This Privacy Policy tells you:**

  * What information we collect
  * How we use that information
  * How we may share that information
  * How we protect your information
  * Your choices regarding your personal information

INFORMATION WE COLLECT

**Information You Give Us**

We receive and may store any information you enter on our websites or give to us in our stores. For example, we collect information from you when you place an order, create an account, call us with a question, create a Wish List, write a review, or use any of our services.

The information we collect from you includes things like:

  * Your name
  * Your mailing address
  * Your e-mail address
  * Your phone number
  * Your credit card number and other payment information
  * Your driver's license number
  * Credit application information, such as your Social Security Number
  * Demographic and lifestyle information, such as age, personal interests and product preferences

It may also include information you give us about other people, such as the name and address of a gift recipient, or the name and contact info of a Friends & Family Pickup person.

**Information From Other Sources**

We may also receive information about you from other sources, including third parties that help us update, expand and analyze our records and identify new customers.

**Automatic Information**

Like many other websites, we also collect information through cookies and other automated means. Cookies are commonly used by websites to save data on your computer. The information we collect from cookies may include your IP address, browser and device characteristics, referring URLs, and a record of your interactions with our websites. We use cookies to create a more personalized shopping experience on our websites.

One type of cookie may allow us to identify you as a particular Best Buy retail store customer when you visit our websites and to link your activities on our websites to your interactions with us in our stores. In combination with other information we collect, this cookie may facilitate the tailoring of advertisements and offers to you, sometimes in connection with interest-based advertising.

To help us understand and enhance our interactions with visitors to our websites, we may permit web analytics providers to collect information on our websites using automated tools like cookies or web beacons. We also may share personal information with those providers. We may have similar arrangements with interest-based advertisers. Interest-based advertising is covered in more detail below.

**Public Forums  **

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them.

HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

We use the information we collect for things like:

  * Fulfilling orders and requests for products, services or information
  * Processing returns, exchanges and layaway requests
  * Tracking and confirming online orders
  * Delivering or installing products
  * Managing our Reward Zone program
  * Marketing and advertising products and services
  * Conducting research and analysis
  * Establishing and managing your accounts with us
  * Communicating things like special events, sweepstakes, promotions and surveys
  * Processing Best Buy credit card or Reward Zone MasterCard applications
  * Identifying you on our websites and tailoring advertisements and offers to you (both on our websites and on other websites) based on your interactions with us in our stores and online
  * Facilitating interactions with Best Buy and others, such as enabling you to email a link to a friend
  * Operating, evaluating and improving our business

**Data Retention**

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

HOW WE SHARE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

**Expeditelectronics** does not sell, rent or trade your personal information to third parties.

We may share your information with third parties to perform services on our behalf such as:

  * Fulfilling orders
  * Delivering packages
  * Scheduling and performing installations
  * Servicing products
  * Maintaining our Reward program
  * Sending marketing communications
  * Fulfilling subscription services
  * Conducting research and analysis
  * Processing credit card payments

Sometimes we may be required to share personal information in response to a regulation, court order or subpoena. We may also share information when we believe it's necessary to comply with the law. We also may share information to respond to a government request or when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property or safety of **Expeditelectronics** , our customers, or others; to prevent harm or loss; or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual unlawful activity.

We may also share personal information in the event of a corporate sale, merger, acquisition, dissolution or similar event.

HOW WE PROTECT THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

When you are buying online from **Expeditelectronics** , we use reasonable security measures to protect the confidentiality of personal information under our control and appropriately limit access to it. We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk.

We use a variety of information security measures to protect your online transactions with us. **Expeditelectronics** uses encryption technology, such as Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), to protect your personal information during data transport. SSL protects information you submit via our Web site such as ordering information including your name, address and credit card number. Information you provide to us via our in-store kiosk does not traverse the public Internet.

YOUR CHOICES REGARDING THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

You may choose to:

  * Stop receiving marketing or promotional e-mails, direct mail, phone and mobile marketing communications
  * Update and correct your personal information
  * Cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services
  * Request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum by contacting us at [cs@expeditelectronics.com](mailto:cs@expeditelectronics.com)

INTEREST-BASED ADVERTISING

We use third-party advertising companies to display ads when you visit our websites or other sites on the Internet. These companies may collect information about your visits to this and other websites. We may also share personal information with these companies. **   **In either case, the purpose is to provide ads about products and services that may be of interest to you.

LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES

Our websites link to other websites, many of which have their own privacy policies. Be sure to review the privacy policy on the site you're visiting.

HAVE QUESTIONS?

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, we'll do our best to answer them by contacting us at [cs@expeditelectronics.com](mailto:cs@expeditelectronics.com)

### Computing Cookies

When you are browsing websites on the internet, usually the websites store the cookies on your computer to help track your use of the site and to personalise your journey around the website. These cookies can be stored so that if you return to a website, that website server can call the information from the cookies stored on your computer to tailor your experience of the site.

**Expeditelectronis.com** use cookies to help you shop our website more effectively and to place online orders -  **we do not store personally identifiable information in our cookie data**. We also use some carefully selected 3rd party suppliers to enhance your online experience and they will place cookies on your computer for use on our website too.

Cookies are perfectly safe to be stored on your computer and almost all web browsers have cookie storing enabled as default. However, all browsers have the option of disabling cookies being stored on your computer if you wish to do this.

**Please be aware**  that disabling cookies on your browser will reduce your ability to shop online with **Expeditelectronis.com**. We use cookies to process products in your basket and orders. Disabling your cookies will mean you cannot purchase through our website. This would also be a common experience of reduced functionality across many websites.

Recent legislation from the European Union has meant that websites must provide clear information about their use of cookies to their customers. We want to ensure that you, as our valued customer, are fully aware of the use of cookies on our website, and we are proud of our reputation as a transparent and honest retailer that you can trust.

We want to make sure you are fully aware of the cookies we use and what they do when you are shopping on **Expeditelectronis.com**.

**Google Analytics:**

We use Google Analytics to help provide us data about the way our customers use our websites to improve your experience. Google Analytics cookies record visitors, city locations, browser type and site journey. Google Analytics cookies do not record personal information. For a full description of Google’s use of cookies please visit:

[**http://code.google.com/apis/analytics/docs/concepts/gaConceptsCookies.html**](http://code.google.com/apis/analytics/docs/concepts/gaConceptsCookies.html)

**Google adwords conversion tracking:** ****

This is a cookie from Google that helps us to understand how customers are purchasing from our website. This information helps us understand what is working more successfully for us in terms of sponsored advertising on search engines, website structures, promotions and other key identifiers. The cookie does not contain any personal information about our customers.

[**https://support.google.com/adwords/bin/answer.py?hl=en &answer=93148**](https://support.google.com/adwords/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=93148)

These are all the cookies currently used by our website and our approved suppliers. Hopefully it is clear that all of our cookies are used ultimately to improve the journey for our customers online or to help us present a better website experience online. 

If you feel you would like to change your personal interaction with cookies, you can adjust storage of cookies settings through your web browser by checking out our [ **Cookies & Your Computer**](http://www.pcworld.co.uk/gbuk/privacy-on-pc-world-157-commercial.html#tab-3) page.

**_Please be aware_**  disabling cookies will severely limit your ability to shop on expeditelectronics.com and disable features of many websites across the internet. 

**Sharing our pages online  **You are able to share certain pages with your friends and networks through 3rd party sites such as [ **Facebook**](https://www.facebook.com/help/?page=176591669064814), [ **Twitter**](https://twitter.com/privacy) and [ **Google+**](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/). If you choose to share via these networks, you may have cookies from these networks stored on your computer. These cookies are not something we control and are sent to you by the 3rd party site you share through – click the links above to learn about the network’s policy on privacy and cookies.
